嘿
Hey!
救命
Help!
救命  救命
Help! Help!
我操
Fuck.
好了 好了 好了
Okay, okay, okay. Okay.
号码是多少  号码是多少
Okay. What was it? What's the number? What's the number?
1  2  1...
1-2-1...
我艹
FUCK!
哪里去了
Where is it?
-911  请稍等  -不  等一下  求你了
-MALE OPERATOR: 911. Please hold. -No! Wait! Please!
-你好  911  -你好 我被埋了
-FEMALE OPERATOR: Yes. 911. -Hello. I'm buried.
你必须救我 我不能呼吸了
You have to help me. You have to help me. I can't breathe.
-先生  -我被埋在了一个棺材里  请救救我
-Sir? -I'm buried in a coffin. Please, help.
-请派人来找我 -请说慢点
-Send someone to find me. -Sin slow down.
-你的名字是什么?  -保罗 保罗 康罗伊
-What is your name? -Paul. Paul Conroy.
好的  康罗伊先生你能告诉我你的位置吗
Okay, Mn Conroy. Can you tell me your location?
我不知道我在一个棺材中
I don't know. I'm in a coffin.
我不知道在哪里请救救我  我好害怕
I don't know where. Please, help. I'm scared.
-你在一个棺材中? -是的
-You're in a coffin? -Yes.
就像那种老式的  木质的棺材
It's like one of those old, wooden ones.
-你在殡仪馆吗?  -不 不 不
-Are you at a funeral home? -No. No. No.
我其实不知道
I don't know. No.
那你怎么给我打电话?
(DISTORTED) How are you calling me right now?
什么
What?
如果你被埋在棺材里  那你从哪里给我打电话
If you're buried in a coffin, where are you calling me from?
用手机  棺材里有一个旧手机
From a cell phone. There was an old cell phone in the coffin.
-你用你的手机给我打电话?  -是的
-You're calling me from your cell phone? -Yes.
是的 是的不是 不是 这个不是我的手机
Yes. Yes. No, no. It's not my cell phone,
但是  我确实用手机给你打的电话
but, yes, I'm calling from a cell phone.
你爬进去棺材的时候里面有个手机?
There was a cell phone in the coffin when you climbed in?
是的 什么?
Yes. What?
-我没有爬进来   -那你怎么进去棺材的 先生
-I didn't climb in, though. -How did you end up in the coffin, sir?
-我是被放进来的 -在一个棺材里?
-I was put here. -In the coffin?
是的  请救救我
Yes. Please, help.
-你说棺材是被埋了的? -是的
-And you're saying the coffin is buried? -Yes. Yeah.
我是一个卡车司机 我是一个美国人
I'm a truck driver. I'm an American.
这里很热 我不能呼吸了
It's hot in here, and I can't breathe.
-求求你了 -你知道你的位置吗
-Please. -Do you know your location, sir?
-我告诉你了 在伊拉克的某地 请救我 -伊拉克?
-I told you, somewhere in Iraq. Please, help. -Iraq?
是的  我是一个卡车司机 一个美国人 为CRT工作
Yes. I'm a truck driver. I'm an American. I work for CRT.
-你是一个军人吗 先生 -不 你必须听我说
-Are you a soldier; sir? -No, please, you have to listen to me.
我是一个卡车司机 一个美国人
I'm a truck driver. I'm an American.
我是一个在伊拉克工作的平民合同商我们在巴格达受到攻击
I抦 a civilian contractor working in Iraq. We were attacked in Baqubah.
然后 他们开枪杀了他们
And they... They shot all of them.
-他们杀了谁? -其他司机
-They shot who, sir? -All of the other drivers.
你说这些都发生在伊拉克?那个国家?
And you are saying this happened in Iraq? The country?
是的  请认真听我说
Yeah. Please, listen to me, okay? Listen to me.
他们给了我一个安全号码在我钱包里 但是现在我不知道哪去了
They gave me a safety number and it was in my wallet, and I don't know where it is now.
康罗伊先生 这里是俄亥俄州的扬斯敦911
Mr Conroy this is 911 emergency in Youngstown, Ohio.
-俄亥俄州? -是的
-Ohio? -Yes, sir.
我不知道你是怎么从另外一个国家打电话到这里的
I'm not sure exactly how you called here if you're in another country but if you'd like,
如果你想要 我可以帮你转接县郡治安部
I can patch you through to the sheriff's department.
你不明白 算了
You don't understand. Forget it.
好的 好的 好的
Okay, okay, okay. Okay. Okay.
接电话 接电话
Pick up, pick up, pick up.
接电话
Pick up.
感谢致电康罗伊一家  我们现在不在家
SHANE: Thanks for calling the Conroys. We're not home right now.
请在B声后留言 谢谢
Please leave a message after the beep. Thanks!
琳达 琳达 亲爱的 是我
Yeah, Linda. Linda, honey, it's me.
我需要你马上联系国民警卫队
I need you... I need you... I need you to contact the National Guard right away,
或者五角大楼
or the Pentagon.
告诉他们我们在巴格达的迪亚拉省受到攻击
Tell them that we were attacked in the Diyala province, in Baqubah.
他们需要找到我
They need to find me. Okay?
求求你 宝贝 你必须帮助他们找到我
Please, baby, you've got to help them find me.
-我是琳达 -不
-Hi, this is Linda. -No!
请留下你的口信 祝你有愉快的一天
Please leave a message. Thanks and have a great day.
琳达 琳达 我需要你马上打电话给我
Linda! Linda, I need you to call me right away, okay?
打这个电话给我 万分火急
Call me at this number. It's an absolute emergency.
打你手机上显示的这个号码 好吗
Call me at the number that comes up on your screen right away. Okay?
我不知道他妈的到底发生了什么 但是
I don't know what the hell is going on, but...
我被埋在了一个棺材里
...I'm buried in a box.
I'm buried in a box.
我不能呼吸了
I can't breathe in here.
收到后请马上打给我 求你了
Call me whenever you can. Please, baby.
哪个州哪个城市?
OPERATOR: What city and state, please?
我不知道 只要是FBI就行
I don't know. The FBI, wherever they are.
你想联系哪个指定的城市吗?
Do you have a specific city you抎 like to be connected to?
随便哪个都行只要是FBI就行
Anywhere. Any city. Just connect me to the FBI.
先生  可以帮你转接的有波士顿
Sir; I have FBI Held of Hoes listed in Boston,
芝加哥  纽约  费城..
Chicago, New York, Philadelphia...
-无所谓 -纽黑文市的FBI
-It doesn't matter. -New Haven...
随便哪个城市 只要帮我转接 求你了
Any city, anywhere. Just connect me, please.
不好意思 先生 但是我们不能那么做
I'm sorry, sir; but i'm not allowed to do that.
-芝加哥 行了吧 芝加哥 行吗? -没必要这么生气 先生
-Chicago! Fine? Chicago! Okay? -There's no need to be rude, sir.
请稍等
Please, hold for your number
你拨打的号码
The number you requested...
3-1-2
4-2-1
6-7-0-0
要额外收取25美分的费用
can be connected for an additional charge of 25 cents
按1键
by pressing the number 1.
芝加哥办公室 哈里斯特别探员
Chicago field office. Special Agent Harris.
-是联邦调查局吗? -是的 先生
-Is this the FBI? -Yes, it is, sir.
好的  我从伊拉克电话过来的
Okay. I'm calling from Iraq.
我被埋在了沙漠的某个地方 我需要你救我
I'm buried in the desert somewhere. I need you to help me.
哇哇 请说慢点
Whoa. Whoa. Sin slow down.
-你什么时候在伊拉克? -现在
-When were you in Iraq? -Now.
我现在就在伊拉克 我是一个卡车司机
Now. I'm there now. I'm a truck driver.
我为CRT工作 我来这里9个月了
I work for CRT. I've been here for nine months.
-请问你的名字是什么? -保罗 康罗伊
-May I have your name, please, sir? -it's Paul Conroy.
保罗 康罗伊
Paul Conroy.
是
Yeah.
好的 保罗 跟我解释下到底怎么了
Okay Paul, explain to me what's going on.
好的 好的
All right, all right. Okay.
好的 我和另外一队司机
All right, me and a convoy of other drivers
我们运送一些厨房用品去一个社区中心
were delivering some kitchen supplies to a community center.
然后有一群孩子 他们朝我们卡车上扔石头
And then some kids, they started throwing rocks at the trucks.
然后 有个路边炸弹在前面炸毁了其中一辆卡车
And then, an IED went off up ahead and it blew up one of the other trucks.
然后有一群人从屋子后面跑出来
And then these guys, they came out from behind the houses
他们开始朝着街上的人开枪
and they started shooting everyone right there on the street.
-你中枪了吗? -我不知道
-Were you shot at? -I don't know.
我不知道 我在车队的很后面
I don't know. I was way in the back of the convoy.
我猜我被人用石头砸到了头
I guess I got hit in the head by one of the other...
然后我昏迷了 这就是我最后记得的事
By one of the rocks and I blacked out, and that's the last thing that I remember.
然后我就在这个棺材醒来 被绑着
And then I woke up here, tied up, in a coffin.
-谁把你放在里面? -我想应该是伏击我们的那些人
-Who put you there? -I guess whoever ambushed us.
-一群小孩?  -不 不 不
-A bunch of kids? -No. No, no, no, no, no.
那些孩子 他们朝我们扔石头
Some kids, the kids, they threw the rocks at us.
那几个男人 应该是伊拉克人 或许是叛乱者 我他妈怎么知道
These guys, some Iraqis, some insurgents. I don't fucking know.
他们突然跳出来就开始朝
They just... They popped out and they started shooting everybody...
-街上的人们扫射 -我想你说过他们没有射到你
-right there on the street. -I thought you said they didn't shoot at you.
是没有 他们杀了他们
They didn't! I don't know. They shot them!
不要再那里大吵大喊了
Sin you're gonna have to stop shouting.
我会大喊大叫是因为你没有认真听我说
I'm shouting because you're not listening to me!
我需要你来救我
I need you to help me!
好的 好的 我明白了
Okay. Okay, okay. I got it.
你能跟踪这个电话吗?GPS之类的
Can you trace the call? GPS or something?
为什么他们没有开枪射你
Why is it that they didn't shoot you?
我不知道 我只知道他们没有对我开枪
I don't know. I have no idea. They didn't. That's all I know.
你的社会保险号是多少 保罗
What's your social security number, Paul?
为什么
Why?
什么 谁在意这个
Why? Who cares?
我被埋在了沙漠中间
I'm buried in the middle of the fucking desert,
谁他妈还在意我的社保号是多少
who cares what my social security number is?
我是一个美国公民 派人过来救我
I'm an American citizen. Just send someone to find me. Please!
你知道你在哪里...
Do you have any idea where...
什么?等等  我听不到你
What? Hold on, hold on. I can't hear you.
你说...等等...我不能...
What did you... Hold on, hold on. No, no, no. I can't...
操
Shit!
Fuck.
快
Come on.
欢迎致电克里斯汀 罗兰 汤玛士公司
Thank you for calling Crestin, Roland and Thomas.
我能帮你转接给谁?
How may I direct your call?
谁都行 我需要跟人说话
Somebody. I need to talk to somebody right away.
-这是紧急情况 -请问你是谁?
-It's an emergency. -Who is this, please?
我是保罗 康罗伊
It's Paul Conroy.
我是为你们工作的司机 我从伊拉克打电话来
I'm a driver for you guys. I'm calling from Iraq.
-我的车队被袭击了 -如果这是紧急情况
-My convoy was attacked. -Sin if this is a crisis situation,
你要拨打分配给你的安全号码
you need to contact the safety number you were...
我知道 我知道
I know. I know. I know.
我没有那个号码 那群人把它拿走了
I don't have it anymore. The people took it.
谁拿走了?
Who took it, sir?
我不知道 我想是伊拉克人  我昏过去了
I don't... I don't know. The Iraqis, I think. I blacked out.
我将把你的电话转给阿兰 达文普
I'm going to ,out you through to Alan Davenport.
-那是谁? -人事主管 请稍等
-Who's that? -Director of personnel. Please hold.
人事?不 不 不 请等等
Personnel? No, no, no, no! Wait, wait, wait!
在CRT公司  我们和顾客一起工作
At CRT, we work with our clients
为他们在快速增长的全球经济遇见的挑战
to provide effective and sustainable solutions
提供有效的和可持续的解决办法
to the challenges they face in our fast-growing, global economy.
你拨打的是克里斯汀 罗兰 汤玛士公司
You've reached Alan Davenport,
人事部主管 阿兰 达文普
Personnel Director at Crestin, Roland and Thomas.
请在B声后留下你的名字和电话
Please leave your name and number at the tone,
我会尽快给你回电
and I will return your call as soon as possible.
我是保罗 康罗伊 我来自密歇根州的黑斯廷斯
This is Paul Conroy. I'm from Hastings, Michigan.
我是CRT公司的司机
I'm a driver for CRT.
我的车队被恐怖分子还是叛乱者伏击了
My convoy was ambushed by terrorists, or insurgents. I don't know.
我不知道是谁 我被困住了
I don't know who it was. And I'm stuck.
我被埋在地下的一个棺材里 我需要帮助
I'm buried in a coffin in the ground, and I need help.
求求你派人过来救我
Please send help. I'm begging you.
我想我在迪亚拉省巴格达附近
I think I'm in Baqubah in the Diyala province.
我不大清楚 请马上派人过来救我
I'm not sure. Please. Please send help right away.
我不能呼吸了
I can't breathe in here. I can't breathe.
我不知道我还能打给谁 请救...
I didn't know who else to call. Please, send...
操 我操
Fuck! Fuck!
我操
FUCK!
快
Come on.
喂 有人在吗
Hello? Is anybody there?
喂
Hello?
-喂?-呼吸还是不呼吸  美国人?
-Hello? -JABIR: Breathe no breathe, American?
-呼吸还是不呼吸? -等等
-Breathe no breathe? -Wait, wait. Hold... Hold on.
我不知道你在说什么 你是谁
I don't know what you're saying. Who is this?
美国人能呼吸还是能不呼吸?
American can breathe no breathe?
我不能呼吸 请把我弄出去
No, I can't breathe. Please get me out of here.
-出去? -是 是 让我出去
-Get out? -Yeah, yeah. Get me out.
让我出去 救救我
Get me out. Please help.
-军人 -不 不 我不是军人
-Soldier -No, no. I'm not a soldier.
我是一个卡车司机 只是一个合同商而已
I'm a truck driver. Just a contractor.
-合同商? -是 合同商
-Contractor? -Yeah, yeah, a contractor.
就这样 不是军人
That's all. No soldier.
-布莱克沃特 -不 不是布莱克沃特
-Blackwater -No. Not for Blackwater.
我不是安保合同商 我只是一个卡车司机
I'm not a security contractor. I'm just a truck driver. That's all.
-你是美国人? -是的
-You American? -Yeah.
那就是军人
Then you soldier
不 我不是
No, I'm not.
我们没有武器 但是你们仍然向我们开枪
I'm here, unarmed. But you still shot at us.
你们的头和喉咙 所以不要再说谎了
In head and in throat, so you tell no more lies.
不 我们没有说谎 我们全都是司机
No, I'm not lying. We were all drivers.
-什么司机? -卡车 卡车司机
-Drive what? -Trucks. Trucks.
那些装满补给品的卡车
The trucks you see driving around with supplies.
那就是我 就是我们 我们不是军人 只是卡车司机
That's me. That's us. That's all. Not a soldier. Truck driver.
-五百万 钱 -什么?
-Five million, money. -What?
今晚9点给我五百万 否则你就像狗一样埋在那里
Five million, money tonight, 9:00 p.m., or you stay. Buried like dog.
-五百万美金  找谁要? -你家庭
-$5 million? From who? -Your family.
我家人没有五百万 如果他们有 我就不会在这里了
My family doesn't have $5 million. If they did, I wouldn't be here.
从美国大使馆要
From embassy.
是是是 从大使馆要
I don't know. Yeah, yeah, from the embassy.
如果你让我从这里出来 他们会给你钱
If you let me out of here, they'll pay you the money. Yeah.
今晚9点 五百万
9:00 p.m., five million, money.
天啊 你的号码是多少
Oh, God. What's your number?
-哪个城市? -密歇根州哈斯廷斯
-OPERATOR: What city and listing, please? -Hastings, Michigan.
我找多纳 米切尔
I'm looking for Donna Mitchell.
这里有两个多纳 米切尔
I have two Donna Mitchells, sir.
一个在联邦路 一个在阿德摩尔林荫道
One on Federal Road and one on Ardmore Avenue.
阿德摩尔林荫道 我想是这个 不  操
Ardmore Avenue. I think. No. Shit!
我不知道 就给我那个吧
I don't know. Yeah, just give me that one.
-阿德摩尔林荫道? -是的 阿德摩尔林荫道
-Ardmore Avenue? -Yes, Ardmore Avenue.
请记住你要的号码
Please hold for your number
你拨打的号码...
The number you requested...
269-148
1998 马上...
1998 can be...
快
Come on.
人呢
Where is everybody?
-你好? -多纳 我是保罗
-DONNA: Hello? -Donna, it's Paul.
-嘿 最近怎样 -还好
-Hey. How's it going? -Okay.
我想要跟琳达说话 她没有接我的电话
I need to talk to Linda. She's not answering her phone.
我遇见难题了
I've got a problem.
我被一群人抓住为人质了
I've been held hostage by a group of guys that...
骗你的 我其实不在家
Fooled you. I'm not really home.
但是如果你留下口信 我会尽快给你回电 拜拜
But if you leave a message, i'll get back to you as soon as I get in. Bye-bye.
多纳 我需要跟琳达说话 情况万分火急
Donna, I need to talk to Linda. It's an absolute emergency.
让她打给我 用来电显示的号码
Have her call me. Use star 69 to find out the number of this phone
然后让她打给我 好吗
and have her call me at this number, okay?
-保罗? -多纳
-DONNA: Paul? -Donna.
-你想要什么? -我需要跟琳达说话 她在哪里
-What do you want? -I need to talk to Linda. Where is she?
我不知道 我一天没和他说话了 打她手机试试
I don't know. I haven 't talked to her all day. Call her cell. ..
-你在你电脑边吗? -是的 怎么了
-Are you at your computer right now? -Yeah. Why?
好 我需要你帮我找个政府部门的号码
Okay, I need you to look up a number for me to the State Department.
保罗 我正要去超市 我真的...
Paul, I was just heading out to the supermarket. I really...
求你了 就帮我找个电话号码
Please, please, please. Just look up the number for me.
-一切都好吗? -不 一切都不好
-ls everything all right? -No! Everything is not all right!
-就帮我找个电话号码 -不要对我喊叫
-Just look up the number for me. -Don 't fucking yell at me...
-我没有对你喊叫 多纳 -不 你有
-I'm not yelling at you, Donna. -Yes, you are.
不 我没有 快给我他妈的电话号码
No, I'm not. Just get me the fucking number!
给我电话号码 给我他妈的电话号码
Get me the number! Get me the fucking number!
操
FUCK!
你他妈的婊子
You stupid fucking cunt!
操
FUCK!
操  婊子
Fuck you, bitch! Fuck you!
操
Fuck you!
-什么? -多纳 我真的很抱歉我对你喊叫
-DONNA: What? -Donna, I'm very sorry that I yelled at you.
我不应该这么做
I shouldn't have done that.
我最后求你一次给我那个电话号码
But I'm only going to ask you one more time to get me this number,
否则 我会死的
and if you don't, I'm gonna die.
-什么? -求求你 我没有时间解释了
-What? -Please, I don't have time to explain.
-那个号码 -好吧 等等
-The number. -Okay, hold on.
-好 政府部门 -是的
-Okay. State Department. -Yeah .
-202 -202
-It's 202... -202.
-134... -134.
-4 750. -4750?
-好了 -好的 去死吧
-Yeah. -Okay. Fuck you.
美国政府
MAN: United States Department of State.
我是一个在伊拉克工作的美国公民 我被绑架了
I'm an American citizen, working in Iraq. I've been taken hostage.
-我需要跟某人谈谈 -你从哪里打电话来 先生
-I need to speak to someone right away. -Where are you calling from, sir?
从伊拉克 我是一个卡车司机
From Iraq. I'm a truck driver.
为克里斯汀 罗兰 汤玛士公司工作
I work for CRT. Crestin, Roland and Thomas.
我的车队被袭击了然后我被抓住了
My convoy was attacked and I'm being held for ransom.
-绑匪跟你在一起吗? -不 我被埋在某个地方
-Are the kidnappers with you? -No. I'm buried somewhere.
-你被埋了? -是的 在一个棺材里
-You're buried? -Yeah. Yeah, in a coffin.
这是一个木制的箱子 一个老式的木制棺材
It's a wooden box, an old wooden coffin.
你有尝试联系外面的军队吗?
Did you try contacting the military out there?
他们给了一个安全号码给我
They gave me a number to call, a safety number.
-但是绑匪拿走了 -他们挟持你为人质?
-But the people took it. -The people holding you hostage?
-是的 是的 -我不知道
-Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. -I don't know.
-稍等 我帮你转接....-不 不要让我等
-Hold on. Let me connect you... -No, don't put me on hold! No!
-丽贝卡 布朗宁 -你好?
-Rebecca Browning. -Hello?
你好 我刚被告知你的情况
Yes, hello. I was just informed of your situation.
是的 我的情况
Yeah, my situation.
我快没有时间了 但是你们的人一直让我等
I'm running out of time and you guys keep putting me on hold.
-你他妈怎么了 -对不起
-What the hell is wrong with you? -I'm sorry.
不要道歉 救我
Don't be sorry. Just help me.
我有几个问题想问你 康罗伊先生
I just have a few questions for you, Mn Conroy.
-你肯定在开玩笑 -了解这些信息对我们
-You've got to be kidding me. -it's important that I get this information.
-对我们营救你非常重要  -等等
-It抣l help make a rescue attempt... -Wait, wait. Hold on, hold on. Wait, wait.
-你怎么知道我的名字? -什么?
-How do you know my name? -I'm sorry?
我的名字 我没有告诉你 我也没有告诉那个男人
My name, I didn't give it to you. I didn't give it to the other guy either.
到底是怎么了
What's going on right now?
我们收到了CRT公司代表的电话 你给他留了口信?
We received a call from a representative at CRT. You left him a message?
-是的 -他马上联系了我们
-Yeah? -He contacted us right away.
所以你知道怎么回事吧
So if you know what the hell is going on,
那你们做了什么来救我出去
then what have you done to get me out of here?
我们从华盛顿能做到的不多
Well, there 's little we can do from Washington.
那只能这样了?因为你能做的不多
So that's it? I'm just supposed to sit here and rot
我只能在这里等着腐烂而死?
because there's little you can do?
-不是的 -那怎样?
-No. -Then what?
我需要知道你的车队在何时何地被伏击
I need to know where you were when your convoy was ambushed.
-在迪亚拉省的巴格达 -好的
-In Baqubah, in the Diyala province. -Okay.
绑匪有和你联系吗
And has contact been made with the kidnappers?
有 他们说今晚9点前要500万美金
Yeah. The guy says he wants $5 million by 9:00 tonight.
好的   然后呢...
Okay or else...
然后他会带我去海洋世界
Or else he'll take me to SeaWorld.
-你他妈到底在想什么  小姐 -我们会尽我们最大的努力
-What the hell do you think, lady? -We'll do everything we can.
那你们会付款吗?
So you'll pay them then? Yeah?
-不 我们不能那么做 -等等 为什么
-No. That we can't do. -Wait, wait. Why?
这是美国政府的政策
It's the policy of the United States government
永远不跟恐怖分子谈判
to not negotiate with terrorists.
不要跟我讲美国政府的政策
Not the policy of the United States government?
小姐 求你了
Lady, come on!
你坐在有空调的办公室里 你说的简单
You're sitting in an air conditioned office, this is easy for you to say.
你不是那个被困在棺材里埋在沙漠中央的那个人
You're not the one stuck in a coffin, buried in the goddamn desert!
-我理解你的沮丧...-沮丧?
-I understand your frustration... -Frustration?
小姐 我他妈会死在这里 你明白吗?
Lady, I'm going to fucking die in here. Understand that?
-喂? -我在
-Hello? -I'm here.
那就说点什么 告诉我你怎么让我离开这里
Then say something. Tell me how you can get me out of here.
好的
Okay.
你的电话号码多少
What's the number on the phone that you're calling from?
-我不知道 你那边没有显示吗?-没有 这边显示保密
-I don't Know. Did it come up on your end? -No. it's listed as unavailable.
告诉我 你记得电话号码吗
Tell me this, can you remember a number?
是的 我有 我有一条铅笔
Yeah. No. I have a... I have a pencil.
-写下这个 -好的 等等
-Okay write this down. -Okay, just a sec.
好的 继续
Okay. Go ahead.
-410 -好
-410... -Yeah.
...195...
-5453. -5453.
-那是谁?-那是丹 布伦娜
-Who's that? -That's Dan Brenner
他是伊拉克人质解救小组的指挥官
He's the commander of the hostage working group over in Iraq.
人质解救小组?
Hostage working group?
在2004年成立来解决类似你这样处境的人
Formed it in 2004 to deal with situations such as yours.
处境我喜欢你这样描述
Situations. I love how you keep calling it that.
-你有记下来吗? -有
-Did you write down the number? -Yeah.
好的  请稍等 我会将你转接给他
Good. Now, just hold on, I 'll connect you with him now.
-他应该在等你电话会 -新闻媒体怎样 我想打给他们
-He should be expecting you. -What about the news? I wanna call them.
不 不要打给媒体
No, don't call the news.
-我重复 不要联系新闻媒体 -为什么
-I repeat, do not contact the news. -Why?
-这只会让情况更加糟糕 -屁话
-It will only complicate things further.. -That's bullshit.
-你只是想掩盖你们的不作为 -不 我只是为了保护你
-You're just covering your own ass. -No, I'm covering yours.
你不去找某样东西 你就不知道它不见了
You don't go looking for something you don't know is missing.
每个人都需要知道我到底怎样了
Everyone who needs to know about this does.
-我需要一切帮助 -我们快没时间了 保罗
-I need all the help I can get. -We are running out of time, Paul.
所以你要马上联系丹 布伦娜
That's why you need to contact Dan Brenner right away.
好
Fine.
我马上转接你
I'm transferring you now.
-布伦娜 -丹 布伦娜?
-Brenner -Dan Brenner?
-是保罗 康罗伊吗? -是的 我是保罗
-ls this Paul Conroy? -Yeah, yeah, it's me. It's Paul.
保罗 我刚被告知你的情况
Paul, I was informed of what's going on.
我希望你知道我们早已经正在想法救你了
I want you to know that we're already working on trying to get you out of there.
谢谢 上帝
Thank you, God.
我被告知截止时间是今晚9点 对吗?
I was told that we have until 9:00 p. m. ls that right?
-那就是绑匪说的 -好的
-That's what he said. -All right.
我们的时间不多
That doesn't give us a whole lot of time.
那些绑匪把你埋在了地下?
And just so I have this right, the kidnappers buried you in the ground?
是的 是一个老的木制棺材
Yeah. It's an old, wooden coffin.
所以我猜你的手机能够收到信号
Okay my guess is that since you're able to get a cell signal,
-你被埋的应该只有几尺深而已 -是啊 我不知道 应该是吧
-you're no more than a few feet underground. -Yeah, I don't know. Maybe.
你的手机电量怎样?还能维持多长时间
What about battery life? How much does the phone have left?
-只剩下一半了 -好的 你必须省着点用
-It's just less than half. -Okay you have to conserve that battery.
我们最大的希望是通过跟踪你的手机找到你
Our best bet of finding you by tracking your cell signal.
-铃声是设置在响铃还是震动状态? -震动
-ls the ringer set on a sound or vibrate? -Vibrate.
我需要你按住*号键不放
I need you to press and hold down the asterisk key
转为响铃状态 这样比较节约电
to change it to a ring tone. It will use less power
-那我的zippo呢?-你有一个打火机?
-What about my Zippo? -You have a lighter?
-是的 -用它来找找附近的标记
-Yeah. -Use it to look around for markings,
商标之类的 -这会燃烧掉氧气吗?
logo, whatever you can find. -Won't it use up oxygen?
现在不用担心这个 试试找找
Don 't worry about that now. Just try to find...
-没有打火机这里好暗好暗 -我理解 保罗
-It's just so dark in here without it. -I understand, Paul.
试试找出能够象征棺材产地的标记
Try to find anything in there that might indicate where that coffin was made.
-你们要尽快 -我们已经在尽我们最大的努力了 保罗
-You guys have to hurry. -We're working as fast as we can, Paul.
你知道还有生还者吗?
Do you Know if there were any other survivors?
-你的车队的人吗? -是的
-From your convoy? -Yeah .
这点还不清楚
Still unclear at this point.
我仅仅只是想做些对我家庭有用的事
I just wanted to do right by my family. That's all.
我不知道会发生今天这样的事
I didn't know it was going to be like this out here.
我想没人能预料到
I don't think any of us did.
-是他 他打来了 -绑匪?
-That's him. He's calling. -The kidnapper?
-是的 我该怎么办 -你知道他的号码?
-Yeah. What should I do? -You know his number?
-是的 -给我
-Yeah. -Give it to me.
-好的  那这通电话怎么办 -先给我电话号码
-Okay. What about the call? -Give me the number first.
-他要挂掉了 -接电话
-He's going to hang up. -Take the call.
-我...好吧  -没事 接电话
-I... Okay. -That's okay, just take the call.
喂  喂
Hello! Hello.
2小时4分钟
JABIR: Two hour; four minute.
-你需要给我多点时间  -你跟大使馆说了吗
-You have to give me more time. -You talk to embassy?
-给钱? -是的 我跟其他人说了
-Give the money? -Yeah, yeah. I talked to someone.
政府说他们不会付钱
The government. They said that they won't pay the money.
-不给钱?  -不给
-No pay? -No.
他们说不和恐怖分子谈判
They said they don't negotiate with terrorists.
恐怖分子?我是恐怖分子?
Terrorists? I am terrorist?
是的 你是恐怖分子 你就是个兔崽子
Yeah. Yeah. You're a terrorist, you son of a bitch.
你害怕了   所以我就是恐怖分子?
You terrified, so I am terrorist?
我对你做了什么
What did I ever do to you?
-做了什么? -是啊
-Ever do? -Yeah.
我来这里是因为工作 我要赚钱
Yeah. I'm here because it's a job, to make money.
-就这样 -你来之前我有工作
-That's it. -I have job until you come.
-现在我的家庭什么都没有了 -那不是我的错
-Now my family have nothing. -That's not my fault!
911不是我的错  但是你们来了
9/11 was not my fault, but you still here.
萨达姆不是我的错 你们又来了
Saddam was not my fault, but you still here.
我告诉过你 我来这里是为了工作  是帮助重建
I told you, I'm only here to work. To help rebuild.
重建你们破坏掉的
Rebuild what you destroyed.
停下来吧 求你了 我仅仅是一个卡车司机而已
Stop! Stop! Just please, stop! I'm just a guy. I'm just a truck driver. Okay?
我没有权力做任何决定
I'm nobody that makes decisions about anything.
我只是想回家
I just want to go home.
喂?
Hello?
-你拍视频 要求赎金视频 -好 好
-You make video. Ransom video. -Yeah, yeah!
如果你让我走  我会拍个视频
I'll make a video. If you let me go, I'll make a video.
不 你现在就拍
No. You make video now.
-什么?现在?  -用手机摄像头
-What? How? -Use video on phone.
纸条在你脚边
Near foot. You read note near foot in box.
-我没看到 -在你脚边
-I don't see it. -Near foot.
-从盒子里面念纸条内容 -好的 好的
-Read note inside box. -Okay, okay.
-如果我拍了视频 你们让我走?  -除非我们收到了钱
-If I make the video, you let me go? -Only if we get money.
没人会为了我给这500万美金的
Nobody's going to pay $5 million for me.
那我们拿少点 100万
We take less. One million, money.
如果他们付钱 你会让我走?
If they pay, you'll let me go?
100万
One million, money.
感谢致电康罗伊一家  我们现在不在家
SHANE: Thanks for calling the Conroys. We're not home right now.
请在B声后留言 谢谢
Please leave a message after the beep. Thanks!
我们很抱歉 你的电话没有连接上 请重新拨打
We're sorry, your call cannot be completed. Please, dial again.
操
Shit.
-保罗? -这是他的号码
-Dan: Paul? -Here's his number.
-请稍等 好的 继续 -好 等等
-Hold on. All right, go ahead. -Okay. Hold on.
号码是07-902-24-921.
It's 07-902-24-921.
好的数据很庞大 除非他们使用克隆电话
Okay. This is huge, Paul. Unless they're using a cloned line,
我们可以在几分钟内查到这是在哪里拨出的电话
we should be able to find where this is coming from in minutes.
好的 我呢?你能追踪到我的手机信号吗?
Okay. What about me? Can you track my cell signal?
追踪你的手机我们遇到很多麻烦
We 're having a lot of trouble with yours.
看起来像是EDS的线路
Seems to be an EDS line,
或许是通过埃及中转的
probably through one of the Egyptian carriers.
什么意思?
What does that mean?
-就是追踪你的电话很难 -他要我拍一个索取赎金视频
-That it's just not going to be easy. -He wants me to make a ransom video.
不 尽量拖延时间
No. Hold off for as long as you can.
如果这能让我离开这里 我会拍的
If it gets me out of here, I'm making it.
我们最不想见到的就是这个视频在半岛电视播放
The last thing we want is for this to end up all over Al Jazeera.
-我们? -是的
-We'? - Yes.
这个不能成为国际性事故
This can't turn into an international incident.
这就是你们在意的?你们在意我吗?
That's all you people care about, isn't it? Don't you care about me?
-我们当然在意 -我呢?
-We do. -What about me?
我们真的在意你 保罗 这就是我为什么在这里的原因
We do, Paul, we do. That's why we're here.
不 不 不 你们不在乎我
No, no, no, you don't! You don't care about me.
你不在乎我们任何人
You don't care about any of us.
我有8个朋友在外面被杀了 今天就死了6个
I've had eight friends killed out here, six of them today.
-听着 保罗 -我们没有枪 没有武装
-Listen, Paul. You just... -We don't have any guns, any armor.
-什么都没有 -那是因为你们不是军人
-Nothing. -That's because you're not soldiers.
这话你去跟那些把我困在这里的人
Tell that to the people who put me in this box!
-保罗 听着 -去跟那些杀了我朋友的人说
-Paul, listen. -Tell that to the people who shot my friends!
-我们在尽最大的努力 -不 你们没有
-We're doing the best we can. -No, you're not! You're not!
-请冷静一点 -我来这里9个月了
-Okay, calm down. -I've been out here nine months.
我知道的 你们这些人仅仅在乎
I know how it works. All you guys care about
你们的秘密计划和后门政策
is your secret plans and your back-room politics.
你知道 如果我是一个外交官
You know, if I was a diplomat,
或者是人质解救小组的领导 或者哪个单位的领导
or a hostage working group leader, or what the fuck your title is,
我早就出去了
I'd be out of here by now.
但我不是 所以我只有坐在这里 闭上我的嘴等死
But I'm not, so I'm just supposed to sit in here, shut my mouth and die.
我需要你注意力集中一点 保罗
Okay, I need you to stay focused, Paul.
草泥马 丹
Fuck you, Dan.
保罗 听我说 找到你是我们的首要大事
Paul, listen to me. Finding you is our primary concern.
底线是 找你就像
Bottom line. And we 're searching for you
找四星上将一样努力
just as hard as we would be for a four-star general,
所以我建议你不要在浪费力气了
so don't literally waste your breath suggesting otherwise.
我不能...我不能...
I can't... I can't...
你受伤了吗 保罗 你还好吗
Are you injured, Paul? Are you okay?
我不知道  他们是谁
I don't know. Who are they?
那些把我困在这里的人是谁
The people who put me in here, who are they?
他们只是人 跟你我没什么区别
They're just that, people. No different from you and me.
-我不是一个恐怖分子 -他们也不是
-I'm not a terrorist. -Neither are they.
你怎么知道
How do you know?
如果你也是无家可归 挨饿...我收回那句话
If you were homeless, starving... Actually I take that back.
如果你的家庭买不起房  挨饿 你会为了他们做什么
If your family was homeless and starving, what would you do for them?
-我不会杀人 -你怎么能这么肯定?
-I wouldn't kill somebody. -How can you be sure?
有区别吗
What difference does it make?
他们是孤注一掷的罪犯
They're criminals, desperate ones at that.
除了钱 他们什么都不在乎
They don't care about anything other than getting the money.
所以付钱 付给他们钱
So pay them, just pay them.
相信我 如果可以这么做 我会毫不犹豫的给钱
Trust me, if it was an option, I would do that in a heartbeat.
有多少人曾经被绑架?
How many others have there been?
-自从我到这里? -是的
-Since I got here? -Yeah.
很多 记者  合同商  军人
Dozens. Journalists, contractors, soldiers.
一堆人曾经被绑架 这是这里唯一正常运转的生意
Dozens have been taken. it's one of the only functioning businesses out here.
你救回了多少人
How many have you rescued?
-多少  -不多
-How many? -Not many.
-告诉我他们的名字 -不
-Tell me their names. -No.
-谁都行 -谁
-Any of them. -Who?
让我相信你真的在乎他们
Make me believe that they really do matter to you.
真的真的在乎他们
That they really do matter to you.
-马克 怀特 -谁是马克 怀特
-Mark White. -Who was Mark White?
一个来自新汉普顿26岁的学生
A kid from New Hampshire. Twenty-six years old. Med student.
来这里帮助当地医生
Came over here to help out local doctors.
他怎样了
What happened to him?
-叛乱者抓了他 -什么时候
-Insurgents grabbed him. -When?
2个星期以前
About three weeks ago.
你记的住他们的名字?
You remember his name?
我记得他们所有人的名字
I remember all their names.
他还...
Is he... Did he?
是的 他还活着
Yeah. Yeah, he's alive.
-他现在在哪里  -家里
-Where is he now? -Home.
或许很高兴的返回学校
Probably happy to be back at school.
我想离开这里
I want to get out of here.
我们找到了他 我们也能找到你
We found him. We抣l find you, too.
怎样找?
How?
通过你给我们的号码我们已经有了确切的线索
We already have a solid lead on the number you gave us.
-你有? -是的 一支队伍已经赶往过去了
-You do? -Yeah. A unit's on its way over there now.
太好了
That's good.
-感觉很好 -是啊
-That feels good. -Yeah.
那我现在应该干什么
What... What should I do in the meantime?
我知道很困难 但是请尽量放松
I know it's hard, but try to relax.
你越挣扎 你就会用掉越多的氧气
The more worked up you are, the more air you're going to use.
好的 我知道了
Okay, I know.
我知道这很困难 因为我有焦虑症
I know. it's hard, 'cause I have anxiety.
我必须吃药
I take pills for it.
-你身上有药吗?  -有
-Do you have them with you? -Yeah.
很好 那就吃吧
Good. Take them.
你必须用尽一切办法来维持你的氧气水平
You need to preserve your oxygen level any way you can.
好的
Okay.
-你的打火机还点着吗?  -没有
-ls your Zippo still lit? -No, not anymore.
-很好 -我感觉想呕
-All right. Good. -I feel nauseous.
-你需要冷静下来 -好的
-You have to calm down. -Okay.
还有你需要节约电量
And you need to save that battery.
我们期待10分钟内会有消息进来
We 're expecting some intel in about 10 minutes.
-到时打给我  -好的
-Call me back then. -Okay.
-坚持住 保罗  -我尽力
-Just hang in there, Paul. - I'm trying, okay.
-什么? -你拍视频?
-What? -JABIR: You make video?
-不 -你拍视频
-No. -You make video!
-让我出去我就拍 -不
-Let me out and I'll make it. -No!
-你现在就拍 -我看不到纸条
-You make video now. -I can't read the paper.
-马上拍视频 -我不能
-Make video now! -I can't.
我不知道你要我说什么 我看不到纸条
I don't know what you want me to say. I can't read the paper.
你 马上拍视频
You make video! Now!
我操
I Fuck!
好 好 快 快
Okay, okay. Come on, come on, come on.
快
Come on!
快啊 快啊 快啊
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
我操
Fuck.
Shit.
山景医院
NURSE: Mountain View Nursing Home.
我希望能跟玛丽 康罗伊通电话
Hi. I was hoping that I could speak with Maryanne Conroy, please.
好的
Okay.
我把电话拿给她 请稍等
Let me bring the cordless phone to her room. Hold on one moment, please.
康罗伊太太 有电话找你
Mrs. Conroy, you have e telephone cell, dean
给你 你能用这个接听
Here, you can use this phone.
喂
Hello?
妈 我是保罗
Mom it's Paul
谁
Who?
保罗 你的儿子
It's Paul, your son.
我有儿子?
I have a son?
没关系 妈妈 你怎样了
It's okay, Mom. How are you?
-我很好 -那就好
-I'm fine. -That's good.
你是谁
Who are you?
我是你的儿子 妈妈 我是小保罗
It's your son, Mom. It's Paulie.
-小保罗 -是的
-Paulie. -Yeah .
记得了吗?曾经住在科法大街  你记得了吗
Remember? Used to live on Colfax Street, in the duplex. You remember?
-小保罗 -嗯
-Paulie? -Yeah .
-没错 -是小保罗吗?
-That's right. -ls this Paulie?
我是小保罗
It is. Its Paulie.
-家里怎样了 -很好
-How's everything at the home? -Very nice.
你爸爸和我每晚都玩琴酒纸牌游戏
Your father and I have been playing Gin Rummy every night.
嗯
Yeah.
我不认为爸爸跟你在一起 妈妈
I don't think Pop's there with you, Mom.
你怎样了 亲爱的
How are you doing, sweetie?
不是很好
Not very good.
这可能是我最后一次跟你谈话了
This might be the last time that I talk to you.
很好 宝贝
That's nice, honey.
你收到我几个月前送的花了吗
Did you get the flowers I sent you a few months ago?
-花? -是的 我送你的 无所谓了
-Flowers? -Yeah, I sent you... Never mind.
我现在要挂了 好吗
Look, I'm gonna get going now, okay?
我晚点再打给你
I just wanted to call and talk to you.
我爱你 妈妈
I love you, Mom.
我说 我爱你 你要跟我说你爱我吗
I said, I love you, Mom. Do you want to tell me that you love me?
是的 你爸爸每晚都跟我玩琴酒纸牌
Yes, dear Your father and I have been playing Gin Rummy every night.
好的 妈妈
Okay, Mom.
你代我跟爸爸问好
You tell Pop I said hi.
不
No.
不 不 不 不
No,no,no,no,no!
No,no,no,no,no,no!
-视频拍了吗?  -求求你 别伤害她
-JABIR: Video make? -Please! Don't hurt her!
-别伤害她 让她走 -你不拍视频 我就杀了她
-Don't hurt her! Let her go. -I shoot if you no make video.
-不 不 不要杀她 -你给我钱 要美金
-No! No! Don't shoot her. Don't shoot. -You get money. American million.
我会的 我保证
I will. I will! I promise.
我保证 求求你了 她是一个母亲 她有2个孩子
I promise. Please, she's a mother. She has two kids.
-2个孩子? -是的 她有2个孩子
-Two kids? -Yes. She has two kids.
我有5个孩子 但是现在只剩下1个
I had five. Now only one.
-你马上拍视频  -等等
-You make video now! -Wait! Wait!
-不 等等 -我给你三秒
-No, wait! -I give three seconds.
-我不知道你要我说什么  -3..
-I don't know what you want me to say! -Three...
-好 好 好 我拍视频 - 2.. 1..
-Okay! Okay! I'll make the video! -Two, one!
我会拍视频 求求你
I'll make the video! I'll make the video! Please, please, please.
我现在挂掉电话马上拍视频 好吗
I have to hang up now to make the video. Is that okay?
你有3分钟来发送视频
You have three minute to send video.
我的名字叫保罗 康罗伊
My name is Paul Conroy.
我是来自密歇根州哈斯廷斯的美国公民
I'm an American citizen from Hastings, Michigan.
我是一个为CRT工作的平民司机
I'm a civilian truck driver for Crestin, Roland and Thomas.
现在我在伊拉克被绑架
And I have been taken hostage somewhere in Iraq.
巴格达时间今晚9点钱我需要1百万美金
I need $1 million by 9:00 tonight, Baghdad time,
否则我会被埋在一个棺材里被撕票
or I'll be left to die here in this coffin that I'm buried in.
我被告知如果付钱了
I'm told that if the money is paid...
我被告知如果付钱了  他们会放我走
I'm told that if the money is paid, I will be let go.
如果没有 我就会在这里死去
If it is not, I will be left to die here.
以上所述都是真实的
These threats are real and will be followed through on.
天啊
Oh, my God.
找到你了
I got you.
找到你了 狗娘样的
I got you, you motherfucker.
找到你了 找到你了 找到你了
I got you. I got you. I got you. I got you.
狗样的
Fucking A. Okay.
快 快 快 接电话
Come on, come on, come on. Pick up, pick up, pick up, pick up, pick up.
你好 我是琳达 请留下口信
Hi, this is Linda. Please leave a message.
祝你有愉快的一天
Thanks and have a great day.
琳达 我找到电话号码了 我找到了
Linda, I figured out the number of the phone. I got it.
我找到了
I got it!
号码是0792-42-884.
Okay. It's 0792-42-884.
打国际电话 记得加代码
Use the international calling code to dial it. I got it, baby.
我爱你 收到马上打电话给我
I love you. Call me as soon as you get this. Call me. I love you.
我操
Oh, shit.
Shit.
好
Okay.
我操 快
Fuck. Come on.
我操
Fuck.
我的名字是帕梅拉 拉蒂
My name is Pamela Lutti.
我是CRT公司旗下
I'm a food service worker at FOB Anaconda,
的员工
employed by Crestin, Roland and Thomas.
抓我的人都要求没有被满足
My captors' requests have gone unanswered.
求求你 求求你 不要
Please. Please, don't!
我的名字是帕梅拉 拉蒂
My name is Pamela Lutti.
求求你了 不要
Please, don't!
如果你被埋在了棺材里面  那么你从哪里打电话来?
If you're buried in a coffin, where are you calling from?
你拨打的电话
The number you requested,
269-948-1998.
他们是孤注一掷的罪犯
They're criminals, desperate ones at that.
除了钱  他们什么都不在乎
They don't care about anything other than getting...
在CRT公司  我们与顾客....
At CRT, we work with our clients to provide...
请不要大喊大叫....
HARRIS: Sin you're gonna have to stop shouting.
今晚9点前给我五百万 否则你就留在这里
JABIR: Five million, money tonight, 9:00 p. m., or you stay.
找到你是目前最紧急的事
DAN: Finding you is our primary concern. Bottom line.
感谢致电康罗伊一家 我们目前不在家
SHANE: Thanks for calling the Conroys. We're not home right now.
请在B一声后留言 谢谢
Please, leave a message after the beep. Thanks!
为什么你要拍那个视频
DAN: Why the hell did you make that video?
-全都是一堆谎言 -什么?
-It's all a bunch of lies. -What is?
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
-全部 -什么全部
-All Of it. -All Of What?
你根本就不在乎我们 我们对你们来说是个屁
You don't give a shit about any of us. We're nothing to you people.
我们会找到你的
We're going to find you.I
滚开 丹 你以为你是保姆吗
Fuck off, Dan. You're babysitting.
你就陪我讲电话直到我死去吧
Just gonna stay on the phone with me until I die.
你不能放弃啊 保罗
Okay. You can't start breaking on me now, Paul.
-你要坚强  -他们杀了她而你们什么都没做
-You have to stay strong. -They shot her and you didn't do anything.
我们不知道她被绑架了
We didn't even know she'd been taken hostage.
-她发了三段视频 -是的  那是他们逼她这么说的
-She sent three videos. -Yeah. That's what they told her to say.
-为什么 -我不知道
-Why? -I don't know.
你知道什么
What do you know?
你的要求赎金视频在youtube上
That your ransom video already has
已经被点击了47  000次了
47,000 hits on YouTube.
所有主流媒体包括半岛电视台都在播放那个片段
And all the major networks are playing it, including Al Jazeera.
所以现在绑匪没有选择只能继续坚持下去
So now your captors have no choice but to follow through.
我找到这台手机的号码了
I found out the number to this phone.
-怎么找的?  -谁在意?
-How? -Who cares?
我找到了 而你没有找到 这是为什么
I figured it out and you didn't. Why?
因为我没有
Because I didn't.
就像你和其他在这个星球上的人
Just like you and every other person on the planet,
有些事我知道 有些事我不知道
there are some things I know, and there are some things I don't.
那我是不是永远都出不去了?
Then how am I ever gonna get out of here?
正如我预料的 他们的信号是克隆的 我们就快找到了
Their signal was cloned, like we figured. But we're close. Really close.
我在一个清真寺附近
I'm near a mosque.
我听到了扩音机上的祈祷文
I heard a call to prayer over the PA.
很好 那意味着我们在正确的区域内
Good. Good. That means that we're in the right area.
你在....
You're...
你在附近?
You're nearby?
我跟护送你们车队的士兵谈过
I spoke with soldiers from the 3rd ID who were escorting your convoy.
他们还活着?
They're alive?
不是全部 基本都被路边的简易炸弹炸伤了
Not all of them. Both Bradley tanks were hit with IEDs.
其余的被一些流弹击伤
The rest got caught in small arms fire
到底发生了什么 保罗
What the hell happened out there, Paul?
保罗
Paul?
等等
Wait.
保罗
Paul?
我操
FUCK!
快 快
Come on. Come on.
Come on. Come on. Come on.
快
Come on.
喂
Hello?
喂 谁在那里?是保罗 康罗伊吗
Hello, who's there? ALAN: ls this Paul Conroy?
是的 我是保罗 你是谁
Yeah, yeah, yeah. it's Paul. Who are you?
保罗 我是阿兰 达文普
Paul, my name 's Alan Davenport.
我是CRT公司的人事部主管
I'm the Personnel Director here at Crestin, Roland and Thomas.
嗯  我给你留了口信
Yeah, yeah. I left you a message.
是的 我也从政府部门的丽贝卡 布朗宁那里听说了
You did. I also heard from Rebecca Browning over at the State Department.
你现在的状况可以说话吗
Are you able to speak on the status of your situation?
更糟了 刚才好像有场爆炸 现在沙子开始灌进来了
It's worse. There was an explosion or something, and the sand's coming through.
估计还有半小时就能灌满这里了
I probably have about half an hour before it fills right up.
你应该尝试冷静下来
Slow down. You should try to stay calm.
那个绑匪 丹 布伦娜来自人质解救小组
The hostage-takers, Dan Brenner from the hostage working group...
好的 保罗 那些媒体怎样了?
Okay, Paul. I'm with you. Now, how about the media?
我知道你的赎金视频泄露了
I know your ransom video leaked,
但是你有跟其他人直接沟通过这件事吗
but have you spoken directly to anyone about what's going on?
-没有 没有  -很好 很好
-No. No, no, no, no. -Good, good, good, good.
你必须这样
It needs to stay that way.
把情况控制好是非常重要的
It's important we keep this situation as contained as possible.
目前的情况是我在一个棺材里
The situation is in a coffin!
我想这控制的非常好 救我 救我
I think it's pretty contained! Help me! Help me!
你正在做什么来救我
What are you doing right now to help me?
我知道你很沮丧 但是我被告知
I know you're upset. But from what I've been told,
他们距离你已经很近了
they're extremely close to getting you out of there.
所以希望不会太长时间
So hopefully it won't be too much longer
-谢谢上帝 -是啊 谢谢上帝
-Thank God. -Yeah, thank God.
现在 我要打开录音机
Now, I'm going to switch on a recorder right now.
-什么?  -等等
-What? -Just a second.
我是阿兰 达文普
This is Alan Davenport,
克里斯汀 罗兰 汤玛士公司的人事部主管
Personnel Director at Crestin, Roland and Thomas Incorporated.
今天是2006年10月23日
The date is October 23, 2006.
我正在和保罗 康罗伊讲话
I'm speaking with Paul Conroy.
康罗伊先生 我在录这段话的时候你是否清醒?
Mr Conroy are you aware that I'm recording this conversation?
-什么?  -请回答这个问题
-What? -Please answer the question.
-操  -康罗伊先生
-Shit. -Mn Conroy?
嗯 嗯
Yeah! Yeah, yeah, yeah.
我有得到你的允许吗?
And do I have your permission to do so?
你为什么需要我的许可?你到底在说什么
Why do you need my permission? What's this about?
我需要回答 有还是没有
I need you to answer yes or no, please.
-有 有 满意吗? -谢谢
-Yes! Yes, all right? -Thank you.
康罗伊先生 你几时受雇于CRT公司?
Now, Mr Conroy, when were you hired by CRT?
我不..9个月以前 大概在1月 到底怎么了
I don't... Nine months ago. Around January. What is all this?
我这里的官方记录显示你受雇于1月4号
I have your official date of hire as January 4th.
-正确吗?  -谁在意?
-ls that correct? -Who cares?
这真他妈的神经病
This is fucking crazy.
-1月4号 正确吗  -正确
-January 4th. ls that correct? -Yes!
在你的前期训练中  在被派遣到伊拉克前
And during your initial training, before being sent to Iraq,
你已经意识到了你所在的职位要承担的风险
you were made aware of the dangers inherent to the position for which you were hired.
你指的是我去达拉斯时你们承诺的所有卡车
You mean when I came down there to Dallas, and you guys said that all of the trucks
都有武装和防弹玻璃?
would be armored and have bulletproof glass?
你指的是你告诉我们这个比任何时候都安全?
You mean when you told us that things were safer than ever over here?
是那个时候..是那个时候我意识到的吗?
Is that when... Is that when I was made aware?
我需要你回答 是还是不是
I need you to answer yes or no, please.
是
Yes.
在那个时候 你是否也收到和CRT
During that time, did you also receive and sign an employment contract with CRT,
签署了详细说明公司政策
which thoroughly explained company policy
和包含了特定条款的就业合同
as it pertained to your specific terms of employment?
是 是 是 我签了一堆东西
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I signed a bunch of things. Yeah.
-是还是不是?  -是 我签了合同
-Yes or no? -Yes! I signed the contract. Yes.
我们也知道了2小时以前
It's our understanding that you were taken hostage in Iraq
你在伊拉克被劫持为人质  正确吗?
two hours ago, is that also correct?
是 我认为那是对目前状况相当客观的评价 你个大屌哥
Yes! I think that's a fair assessment of the situation, you fucking dick.
这些有什么意义?
What's the point of all this?
我们的法律部门要求要一份员工宣誓过的证词
Our legal department requires that we obtain a sworn affidavit from employees,
来证明他们明白公司必须强制解除合同的原因
confirming that they understand the reasons for their forced separation from the company.
从今天早上起 你和CRT公司的合同已经被取消了
As of this morning, your employment with CRT was officially terminated.
等等 等等 你说什么?
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. What?
我们注意到你和一位
It was brought to our attention that you were engaging
前CRT员工帕梅拉 拉蒂有关系
in relations with a fellow CRT employee, Pamela Lutti.
-不 不 不 等等 -你的合同有
-No. No, no. Hold on, hold on. -Stipulated in your contract
交友条款 里面说的很清楚
was a fraternization clause, in which it was stated quite clearly
-任何....   - 等等 请等等
-that any relationship... -Stop, stop, stop. Please.
恋爱还是性关系...
...be it romantic or sexual in nature...
-我们只是朋友  -被认为是不恰当的
-We were just friends. -. . . deemed inappropriate
CRT有权立即终止合同关系
by CRT senior officials is grounds for immediate termination.
等等 好吗  我们只是朋友
Hold on. Okay? We were just friends. We were just friends.
-我们的记录可不是这样 -你的记录是错的
-Our records indicate differently. -Your records are wrong.
我们也正式通知你
We 're also legally required to inform you
因为你从法律上来说
that because you were technically no longer
在你被绑架时你已经不是CRT的员工
under the employ of CRT at the time of your abduction,
所以我们不会负责解雇你后
we cannot be held accountable for any injury
在你身上受到的任何伤害
that may befall upon you after your official date and time of termination.
因此 在你的案件中 包括这次事故
Therefore, in your case, that includes this incident,
还有这次事故导致的任何后果
or any consequences that may result from it.
那我的保险金呢 我家人需要那笔钱
What about my insurance money? My family's gonna need that money.
由于你的合同已经被终止.....
Given that you were alive up until the time of your termination...
不要这样
Don't do this.
-你明白这些吗?  -不要这样做
-Do you understand everything? -Don't do this!
你明白我跟你说的吗 康罗伊先生
Do you understand everything you've been told, Mn Conroy?
康罗伊先生
Mn Conroy?
你就是个狗屎
You're a piece of shit.
和保罗 康罗伊的谈话到底结束
That concludes our interview with Paul Conroy.
我现在关闭录音机
I am now turning off the recorder
你把我放在这里
You put me here.
对不起
I'm sorry.
接电话 接电话
Answer the phone. Answer the phone.
快 为什么你不接电话
Come on. Why won't you answer the phone?
保罗 是你吗
DAN: Paul, is that you?
他们都死了
They're dead.
-你怎么知道? -我就是知道
-How do you know that? -I just do.
3架F16刚才城市上空盘旋
Three F-16s leveled parts of the city a few minutes ago.
嗯 我知道
Yeah, I know.
嗯 那很有趣
Yeah, that was fun for me.
他们知道我在这里吗
Did they know I was here?
-是的  -嗯
-Yeah. -Yeah.
他们在意吗
Did they care?
这些绑匪 如果他们死了
These people that took me, if they're dead,
他们就不能告诉你我在哪
they can't tell you where I am.
我们仍然可以追踪你的信号
We can still try to track down your signal.
你已经试过了
You tried that already.
我们可以再试一次
We can try again.
-都结束了是吧  -不
-It's over, isn't it? -No.
是的
Yeah.
我应该怎么办
What should I do?
我不知道
I don't know.
好奇怪
It's weird.
什么
What is
先知
Knowing.
我希望结果会不一样 保罗
I wish this could have gone differently Paul.
是啊
Yeah.
我也想
Me, too.
我的名字是保罗 斯蒂芬 康罗伊
My name is Paul Steven Conroy.
社保号是048321198 生日是3/23/76.
Social security number, 048-32-1198. Date of birth. 3/23/76.
这段视频是我的最后心愿和遗嘱
This video will serve as my last will and testament.
给我的妻子 琳达 康罗伊
To my wife, Linda Conroy,
我给你留下了700美金在我的个人存款里
I leave you the $700 in my personal savings,
还有剩下的养老金
and whatever's left in my annuity.
给我的儿子 沙恩 康罗伊
To my son, Shane Conroy,
我不知道
I don't know
我没有...我的衣服
I don't have... My clothes.
我给你我的衣服 你会长大的
I leave you my clothes, which you will grow into.
不是这些
Not these ones.
我真的没有....
I don't really have...
我希望我能留下更多给 但是...
I wish that I had more for you, but...
如果我是著名的壁球运动员 或者穿着西装上班的人
Maybe if I was a famous baseball player, or some guy who wore a suit to work...
那样我会拥有更多
Then I'd have more.
但是 你懂的 你能成为那类型的人
But, you know, you can be one of those people if you want. Um...
是啊
Yeah. Yeah.
答应我你长大后你会好好照顾母亲
Just promise me that when you get older that you'll take good care of your mom.
嗯 我不知道
And, I don't know.
你总是尝试做些正确的事
You always try to do the right thing.
我非常爱你 沙恩
I love you very much, Shane.
或许我说的不够 或许够 我不知道
Maybe I never said that enough. Maybe I did. I don't know.
那或许意味着不够
That probably means I didn't. And...
对不起 琳达 我应该听你的
I'm sorry, Linda. I should have listened to you.
你还没有死 喂 喂
You're not dead. Hello? Hello?
钱呢?
JABIR: Where is money?
-我不知道 -什么不知道
-I don't know. -What don't know?
-我不知道在哪里 -骗子
-I don't know where it is. -Liar!
我发誓我没说谎
No, I'm not lying! I swear.
-你发誓? -嗯 我发誓
-Swear? -Yeah, I swear.
-我说的实话 -从大使馆拿
-I'm telling the truth. -From embassy.
-不 -你现在有钱了?
-No. -You get money now!
-我不能够 -你会的
-I can't! -You will!
-我需要多点时间 -没有时间了
-I need more time. Please. -No more time!
沙子正在漏下来
There's sand pouring in here.
到处都是 让我出去 我保证我会给钱你
It's everywhere. Let me out of here, and I promise you I will get you the money.
-你流血 -什么
-You show blood. -What?
-你流血了 他们就给钱 -不
-You show blood, they give money. -No.
你切掉手指 拍视频
You cut finger; send video.
-不 我不会那么做的 -你会的
-No, I'm not doing that. -Yes!
-不 -不?
-No. -No?
不 我不会干的 你让我出去
No, that's right, no. You let me out of here,
我会完整无缺的出去
and I'll out off my whole goddamn hand if you want.
-你有妻子?  -是的
-You have wife? -Yeah, I do.
我还有个年幼的儿子 我还想见到他 求你了 大哥
And a son. I have a young son. And I want to see them again. Please, sir.
-大哥? -是的 大哥
-Sir? -Yes. Sir.
我充满尊敬的叫你大哥
I say that out of respect to you.
美国密歇根州哈斯廷斯北胡桃林街243号
243, North Walnut Street. Hastings, Michigan, USA.
那是我的...你为什么说那个
That's my... Why did you say that?
你流血还是他们流血
You show blood, or they show blood.
你们什么都不是
No. You're nobody, all of you.
你接近不了他们
You can't get to them.
-不?  -不
-No? -No.
你就是个农夫 就是个罪犯
You're peasants. You're fucking criminals, that's all.
你连密歇根在哪里都不知道
You don't even know where Michigan is.
底特律 安娜堡
Detroit. Ann Arbor
你在看地图 你在看地图
You looked at a map. You looked at a map.
你流血还是他们流血 5分钟内发送视频过来
You show blood, or they show blood. Send video by five minutes.
你好  我是琳达请留言谢谢并祝你度过愉快的一天
Hi, this is Linda. Please leave a message. Thanks and have a great day.
琳达!琳达  听我说  你和谢恩必须去某处  好吗?
Linda! Linda, listen to me, you and Shane have to go somewhere, okay?
不要回家  不要回家
Do not go back to the house. Do not go back to the house.
去哪里都好就是不要回家好吗?他们知道我们住在哪里
Just go anywhere but to the house. Okay? These guys, they know where we live.
他们有我的驾照
They have my driver's license.
逼不得已你就去警察局  就是别回家
Just go to the sheriff's station if you have to, just do not go home.
天啊
Holy God.
操
Fuck.
这是丹尼尔布伦纳请留言
This is Daniel Brenner Please leave a message at the tone.
布伦纳  你在哪里?那些家伙仍然活着!
Brenner, where are you? The guy's still alive!
他刚打电话给我  他还活着
He just called me. He's still alive.
操
Fuck.
他们找不到他们
They can't find them. They can't.
没门不  不  不
There's no way. No, no, no, no, no.
他们找不到他们  他们找不到他们
They can't find them. They can't find them. They can't find them.
操
Fuck.
我叫帕梅拉 拉蒂
My name is Pamela Lutti.
我是一个餐馆服务员
I'm a food service worker at FOB Anaconda,
受雇于CRT公司
employed by Crestin, Roland and Thomas. (CRYING)
抓我的人的要求得不到答复
My captors' requests have gone unanswered.
求你了  不要
Please. Please, don't!
操
Fuck.
-绕到那边去  -快 行动
-Around to the other side! -Move it, move it, move it!
我看见他了!!
MAN 1. I see him! Move it!I
回来  大家快回来!
Get back! Everybody, get back!
平民已经找到了  平民已经找到了
Civilian has been located. Civilian has been located.
你还好吗?跟我说话
MAN 3: Are you okay? Talk to me.
保罗  你还好吗?
Paul, are you okay?
什么?
Yeah?
保罗?保罗  我是布伦纳
Paul? Paul, it's Brenner.
-你在那里吗保罗? -我在这儿?
-Are you there, Paul? -I'm here?
我们现在来救你了你听到没?我们找到你了
We 're coming for you now. You hear me? We know where you are.
你们救我来了?-是的  保罗
-You're coming? -We are, Paul.
-我们就在附近了-你怎么知道?
-We 're almost there now. -How do you know?
联军们在巴格达外面抓到了一个反叛者
Coalition forces picked up a Shi'ite insurgent just outside of Baghdad.
说他知道一个美国人在哪里被活埋的
Said he knew where an American was buried alive.
他同意如果我们放他走他就告诉我们在哪里
He agreed to show us where if we let him go.
-你们救我来了?-事实上我们已经到了
-You're coming for me? -We are practically there already.
-你必须...你必须快点-我们很快了  保罗
-You have... You have to hurry. -We are, Paul.
你们必须快点沙子...沙子...
You have to hurry. The sand... The sand...
你只要在那坚持多三分钟
You just hang in there three more minutes.
这一切就要结束了我发誓  保罗
This will all be over soon, I promise, Paul.
好  好我相信你
Okay. Okay. I believe you.
三分钟  保罗我只需要你再坚持三分钟
Three minutes, Paul. I just need you to hang on for three minutes.
-谢谢-这一切就要结束了  我答应你...
-Thank you. -This will all be over soon. I promise you...
-我得走了!打回给我-不  不!保罗  保罗  保罗!
-I have to go! Call me right back. -No, no, no! Paul, Paul, Paul!
-请给我回电!-不  等等  保罗!
-Call me right back. Please! -No, wait, Paul!
琳达!琳达!
Linda! Linda!
保罗?保罗  是你吗?
Paul? Paul, is that you?
-告诉我那是你 -是我
-Tell me it's you. - It's me.
噢  我的天  保罗!他们对你做了什么?
Oh, my God, Paul! What are they doing to you?
-请告诉我你没事-我很好
-Please tell me you're okay. -I'm okay.
我刚刚看了新闻我把手机忘在家里了
I just saw the news. I left my cell phone at home.
他们知道我在哪里他们正要来抓我
They know where I am. They're coming to get me.
那些美国人来救我了
The Americans are coming for me.
-是吗?  -会没事的
-They are? -it's going to be okay.
谢天谢地
Thank God. Thank God.
他们就要来了  他们正在路上  一切会好的
They're coming. They're on their way. it's gonna be okay.
我多么害怕就要失去你
I was so afraid I was going to lose you.
-不会的   -我多么爱你
-You're not. -I love you so much.
-我多么爱你  -我多么爱你
-I love you so much. -I love you so much.
我多么爱你  很抱歉  我本不应该来的
I love you so much. I'm so sorry. I should never have come here.
我本应该听你的话  对不起
I should have listened to you. I'm sorry.
亲爱的  我不管了我只想你回家  回到我身边
Sweetie, I don't care. I just want you home. Please come home to me.
我会回家的  我会回家
I'm coming home. I'm coming home.
-你发誓   -我发誓
-Swear it. -I swear.
-我发誓我会回家   -我爱你  我深深地爱着你
-I swear I'm coming home. -I love you. I love you so much.
我知道
I know.
-他们在这里   -好的
-They're here. -Okay.
他们在这里!我必须走了
They're here! I have to go.
-马上打给我-我会的  我答应你
-Call me right away. -I will. I promise you
-我会的我爱你   -我爱你你发誓
-I will. I love you. -I love you. Swear it.
-我很爱你   -再次发誓
-I love you so much. -Swear it again.
我发誓!我得走了
I swear! I have to go.
-请回到我身边   -我爱你
-Please come home to me. -I love you.
-丹?  -快!快!我们走!
-Dan?  -Move! Move! Let's go!
-布伦娜?   -好的保罗?保罗?我们在这儿!
-Brenner? -Okay Paul? Paul? We're here!
-是我    -他把我们带到你这儿来了
-it's me. -He brought us right to you.
快  快你必须快点它就快满了
Hurry, hurry. You have to hurry. It's almost full. Please.
保罗  在那坚持一下我们就在你上面
Paul, just hang in there. We're right above you.
我不能  我不能坚持了你们在附近?
I can't. I can't. Are you close?
-我们就差不多在那了!-你们在不远处?
-We 're almost there! -Are you close?
我们就差不多在那里了!正上方!
We 're almost there! Right above!
-求求你!我听不到你说什么!   -继续挖
-Please! Please! I can't hear you! -Keep digging!
-我听不见你说什么!你们在哪里?   -我们就在那里了!
-I can't hear you! Where are you? -We 're almost there!
-一直挖!我们看见棺材了   -是的  挖吧
-Keep digging! We see the coffin. -Yeah, dig in...
-坚持住!    -请打开它请打开它
-Hang in there! -Please open it. Please open it.
我们走!快!大伙再快一点  再快一点!
Let's go! Move! Faster guys, faster!
-快点!快!   -好的  明白!
-Hurry up! Hurry! -Okay, okay, clear!
请她妈的快点!
Fucking hurry! Please!
快!
Hurry!
噢  我的天
Oh, my God.
-什么?什么?  -噢  我的天
-What? What? -Oh, my God.
-对不起保罗我很抱歉   -那是什么...什么?
-I'm so sorry Paul. I'm so sorry. -What is... What?
那是马克怀特
It's Mark White.
他把我们带到了马克怀特身边
He brought us to Mark White.
噢  天啊噢  天
Oh, God. Oh, God
-我很抱歉我很抱歉-好的
-I'm sorry. I'm sorry. -Okay.
好的噢  天啊!
Okay. Oh, God.
我很抱歉  保罗  真的很抱歉
I'm sorry Paul. I'm so sorry.